toptenpk.com 2013-12-07

# Privacy Policy | Top Ten Lists or Best Top 10 Lists at TopTenpk.com

This privacy policy is for toptenpk.com

We allow third-party advertising companies (like [Google Adsense](http://www.google.com/adsense/)) to serve ads when you visit our Web site. Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

Please note that these companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies,[click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

Here are some third-party vendors serving ads on this site and you may visit those vendor websites to opt out of cookies (if the vendor offers this capability).

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to [contact us](http://toptenpk.com/contact-us/ "contact us") by email at info gsmtweet@gmail.com

At toptenpk.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by toptenpk.com and how it is used.

Log Files

Like many other Web sites, toptenpk.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

http://toptenpk.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

DoubleClick DART Cookie

.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on http://toptenpk.com

.:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to http://toptenpk.com and other sites on the Internet.

.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include …….

Google Adsense
